https://www.visitmanisteecounty.com/privacy-policy

Twitter
Instagram Follow us #MyManisteeRequest Travel Guides#MyManistee In the NewsPRIVACY POLICYThis Web site, https://www.visitmanisteecounty.com, http://www.manistee-cvb.com, and http://www.visitmanistee.com and http://www.manistee.com is owned and operated by Manistee County Visitors Bureau. We are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our Web site users. The intent of our privacy statement is to inform you, the user, about the information that we may collect about visitors to our site, how we use that information and about our disclosure practices.Manistee County Visitors Bureau is committed to high standards that require honesty, integrity and fairness. Manistee County Visitors Bureau will collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us. We do not use techniques that collect personal information about you without your knowledge. You have the right to decline to have any information collected or transferred for marketing purposes.What happens to your personal information?We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.When Requesting Information.When you request information from us, we will retain your information provided so we can reach out via mail, email or other correspondence. We will also share your information to the interest area providers you select, but only to our direct affiliates.  Your information will never be sold by VisitManisteeCounty.com.What about Cookies, Pixels, Etc.?Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.Our website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies through your browser settings. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Visit Manistee County utilizes tools including, but not limited to: Google Ads and Facebook Pixels, these are cookies/tracking/ad tags dropped on your browser to help in the website experience, by enhancing the delivery of your content across multiple devices and platforms. You may opt out of these by changing your browser settings or disabling in Facebook.What about Spam?Subscribers will not receive any unsolicited emails or correspondence if they have not provided us with prior permission. From time to time, we may use email as a way to keep in touch with our Web site visitors. If you agree to receive email communications from us, every email message we send to you will include an email address to which you can respond. If at any time you decide you do not want to receive marketing email from us, simply let us know and we will remove your name and email address from our mailing list. You may opt out of any of our email lists by selecting this in the footer of the email newsletter.When you leave this siteThis policy discloses the privacy practices for our Web site. However, our site contains links to other sites. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy and security policies of the new site. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all Web sites you visit, especially if you share any personal information.Security Policy Users are prohibited from violating or attempting to violate the security of the site. By way of example, you are prohibited from (a) accessing data not intended for such user or logging onto a server or an account which the user is not authorized to access; (b) attempting to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of a system of network or to breach security without proper authorization; (c) attempting to interfere with serve to any user, host or network; (d) sending unsolicited mail, including promotions and/or advertising of products or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.Service Providers.We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:To facilitate our Service;To provide the Service on our behalf;To perform Service-related services; orTo assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.Changes to this policy.We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.Contact us if you have any questions.If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
